Our secret that you can't reveal
誰にも 言えない 秘密のこと
The truth that no one can know
誰にも 言わない ホントのこと
Our inseparable pair that shares a false sympathy
どこにもいけない二人の噓シンパシー
Beautiful and elegant, yet deceitful are these flowers
華麗で 優雅で 裏切る花
Resembling you are these Dahlias flowers
誰かに よく似た ダリアの花
Everything is about the two of us
すべては ふたりの
Our sweet, deceptive dance
甘い疑惑のダンス
Pain
痛み
[Pain] Give it to me
与えて
A feeling more genuine than love
愛より 確かなもの
Punishing
罰を
I need it from you
与えて
So we can stay together
ずっと 離れないよう
Tangled up in you, you, you, you,,
動けなくなる
You know that I'll never leave you
ほどけない 愛
Tumbling down, down, down, down...
落ちていく
鎖でつながれた 二人の楽園
傷を 与えて
しるしを 遺してほしい
あなた だけでいい
私を 求めていて
誰にも わからない 二人のこと
あなたが 私を 憎むほどに
見えない鎖が肌に食い込む心地
あなたに摘まれる　非力な花
涙は　したたる　蜜の香り
触れては いけない
赤い魅惑の果実
痛み 与えて
愛より 確かなもの
罰を 与えて
ずっと 離れないよう
Tangled up in you, you, you, you,,
抱き合うたび
You know that I'll never leave you
絡まった 愛
Tumbling down, down, down, down...
目を閉じて
噓で操られた 最後の楽園
誰にも わからない 二人のこと
あなたが 私を 憎むほどに
どこまでいっても安心する感覚
誰かの 望んだ 私になる
そしたら いつかは 愛せるかな
乾きも 孤独も 自己欺瞞のシンパシー